FAN FAN FIRGIAWAN

0895-2552-1887 | firgiawan.fanfan@gmail.com | fanfan.vercel.app

PROFILE

I am an Informatics Engineering student at the **University STMIK Bandung**. I am a **Junior Web Developer**, and **Android Developer** who is passionate about learning the technologies needed to solve problems, I strive to provide an engaging and functional user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HEAD OF WAREHOUSE

PT. Roodolph Detik Abadi

April 2023 - Present

- Control the receipt, delivery and storage of goods, as well as manage materials and stock
- Supervise the work of warehouse staff and be a firm leader for them
- Oversee warehouse security
- Responsible for stock accuracy both in terms of data and physical goods
- Ensure that all activities in the warehouse run in accordance with SOPs and company policies
- Ensure the availability of goods according to needs

WAREHOUSE STAFF

PT. Roodolph Detik Abadi

Febuary 2021 - April 2023

- Responsible for storing goods production
- Packaging goods
- Shipping goods

ADMINISTRATIVE STAFF

PT. Pratama Panca Nusantara

November 2018 - May 2020

- Responsible for providing files during auctions
- Also serves as field admin in charge of supervising project progress
- Maintaining IPAL machines and drawing technical designs (Autocad)

EDUCATION

University STMIK Bandung

2022 - Present

Bachelor's degree in informatics engineering

SMAN 16 Bandung

2014 - 2017

High School graduate majoring in science

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication skills
- Negotiation skills
- Problem-solving skills
- Organization and time management skills
- Teamwork
- Multitasking
- Detail Oriented
- LeaderShip

HARDSKILLS & TOOLS

- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- C++
- JavaScript
- JAVA
- Node.js
- React
- MySQL / MariaDB
- Linux

- VMware
- Figma
- Postman
- Arduino
- Bash
- Apache/NginX
- GIT
- GitHub / GitLab
- LARAVEL
- Bootstrap

- PlantUML
- SketchUp
- AutoCAD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe PhotoShop
- Adobe XD
- CorelDRAW
- VBA
- Ms. Excel
- Ms. Word